Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards U.S. House of Representatives papers, Inclusive: 1990-2010, Bulk: 1991-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Speeches, 1989-2009; 10
  - House of Representatives, 1990-2003, undated; 6
    - Floor Speech on War Declaration Regarding Kosovo, c.1995 (Box 177, Folder 49)
    - Floor Speech in Opposition to the Government Shutdown, 1995 (Box 177, Folder 50)
    - House of Representatives: Partial Birth Abortion (HW), 1995 Nov 1 (Box 177, Folder 51)
    - House of Representatives: VA Appropriations Bill (HW), 1995 Dec (Box 177, Folder 52)
    - House of Representatives- Floor Speech (HW), 1995 Dec (Box 177, Folder 53)
    - Floor Statement on Sonny Montgomery Retiring, 1996 (Box 177, Folder 54)
    - House of Representatives: Memorial Service (HW), 1996 Jan 24 (Box 177, Folder 55)
    - House Subcommittee on Texas Military Bases (HW), 1996 April 10 (Box 177, Folder 56)
    - House of Representatives: HR 1350 (HW), 1996 Dec 15 (Box 177, Folder 57)
    - Floor Speech in Favor of Criminal Background Checks on Guns, 1997-2000 (Box 177, Folder 58)
    - Floor Speech on Gun Control, 1997-2000 (Box 177, Folder 59)
    - Floor Speech on Nuclear Non-Proliferation, 1997-2000 (Box 177, Folder 60)
    - House of Representatives: Tax Resolution, 1998 April 22 (Box 177, Folder 61)
    - House of Representatives: Social Security (HW), 1998 (Box 177, Folder 62)
    - Statement on H.Con Resolution 1999, 1999 Nov 2 (Box 177, Folder 63)
    - HCR 94, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 64)
    - House of Representatives Rule of Law (HW), 1999 (Box 177, Folder 65)
    - House of Representatives- Partial Birth Abortion, 2000 March 5 (Box 177, Folder 66)
    - House of Representatives: Impact Aid Program (HW), 2000 May 15 (Box 177, Folder 67)
    - House of Representatives: CE Amendment, 2000 June 21 (Box 177, Folder 68)
    - House of Representatives Human Resources Testimony- Charitable Choice, 2001 June 14 (Box 177, Folder 69)
    - House of Representatives: House Joint Resolution 64, 2001 Sept 14 (Box 177, Folder 70)
    - House of Representatives: HR 815, 2001 (Box 177, Folder 71)
    - House of Representatives: Obligation for Highways, 2002 (Box 177, Folder 72)
    - House of Representatives: War in Iraq, 2002 (Box 177, Folder 73)
    - Floor Speech in Favor of Authorization of Iraq War, 2003 (Box 177, Folder 74)
    - Chet’s Whip Count for Persian (HW), undated (Box 177, Folder 75)
    - Congressional Contact Team: Talking Points on Vouchers, undated (Box 177, Folder 76)
    - Grouped Items Folder, undated (Box 177, Folder 77)
    - House of Representatives: HR 815 (HW), undated (Box 177, Folder 78)
    - House of Representatives: Balanced Budget Amendment (HW), undated (Box 177, Folder 79)
    - House of Representatives: C-17 Debate (HW), undated (Box 177, Folder 80)
    - House of Representatives: Federal Employees (HW), undated (Box 177, Folder 81)
    - House of Representatives: Floor Statement On Impeachment (HW), undated (Box 177, Folder 82)
    - House of Representatives: Gun Regulation (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - House of Representatives: HCR 94, undated (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - House of Representatives: Highway Funding, undated (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - House of Representatives: Homeland Security Appropriations, undated (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - House of Representatives: HR 111 (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - House of Representatives: HR 3, Veterans COLA Bill, undated (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - House of Representatives: Military Insurance System (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - House of Representatives: Protectionism and Tariffs (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - House of Representatives: Protectionism Debate (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - House of Representatives: Floor Speech for Religious Freedom, undated (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - House of Representatives: Sonny Montgomery (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - House of Representatives: Talking Points Against the Resolution, undated (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - House of Representatives: Talking Points for the Armed Forces Tax Fairness Act Included In The Motion To Recommit, undated (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - House of Representatives: Tax Cuts (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - House of Representatives: VA Medical Centers (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - House of Representatives: Veterans, undated (Box 178, Folder 16)
    - House of Representatives: Veterans Budget Debate (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - House of Representatives: Veterans Health Care Budget Amendment (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 3 Floor Speech (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Middle East Issues, undated (Box 178, Folder 20)
    - Milosovic Floor Speech (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 21)
    - Opposition to the Confirmation of Cassin and Greytook (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 22)
  - Impeachment, 1998; 7
    - Candice Kelly/ Clinton Observations (HW), 1998 (Box 178, Folder 23)
  - Luncheon, 1991-1999, undated; 8
    - Congressional Prayer Breakfast (HW), 1991 April 27 (Box 178, Folder 24)
    - Congressman Kika DeLa Garza Luncheon (HW), 1991 June 15 (Box 178, Folder 25)
    - P.R.I.D.E. Awards Luncheon (HW), 1992 April 30 (Box 178, Folder 26)
    - Women’s Equality Day Luncheon (HW), 1993 Aug 30 (Box 178, Folder 27)
    - March of Dimes CEO Luncheon (HW), 1996 Jan 17 (Box 178, Folder 28)
    - TSTC Founders Luncheon/TSTC Foundation (HW), 1998 April 14 (Box 178, Folder 29)
    - African American Leadership Luncheon (HW), 1998 Aug 31 (Box 178, Folder 30)
    - Clinton Scandal/ Trial Observation (HW), 1998 (Box 178, Folder 31)
    - Clinton Scandal Observations (HW), 1998 (Box 178, Folder 32)
    - African-American Leadership Luncheon (HW), 1999 Jan 11 (Box 178, Folder 33)
    - Army Caucus Breakfast (HW), 1999 Feb 3 (Box 178, Folder 34)
    - Army Caucus Breakfast (HW), 1999 June 23 (Box 178, Folder 35)
    - AUSA Luncheon (HW), 1999 Aug 18 (Box 178, Folder 36)
    - Marlin Luncheon (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 37)
    - Texas Breakfast Club (HW), undated (Box 178, Folder 38)
  - Meeting, 1991-2009, undated; 9
    - Town Hall Meeting on Persian Gulf, 1991 March 30 (Box 178, Folder 39)
    - Cedar Park Chamber of Commerce (HW), 1991 Aug 28 (Box 178, Folder 40)
    - “What’s Wrong with Congress?” Waco Rotary Club (HW), 1991 Oct 28 (Box 178, Folder 41)
    - Salado Café (HW), 1991 (Box 178, Folder 42)
    - San Saba Rotary/ Lions (HW), 1992 Feb 13 (Box 178, Folder 43)
    - First United Methodist Church- Waco, TX (HW), 1992 Feb 16 (Box 178, Folder 44)
    - A.U.S.A — Central Texas Chapter (HW), 1992 June 15 (Box 178, Folder 45)
    - Bell County Medical- Temple, TX (HW), 1992 Aug 18 (Box 178, Folder 46)
    - Hamilton Kiwanas Club/ Belton Lions Club (HW), 1992 Sept 2-3 (Box 178, Folder 47)
    - Central Texas Chapter of Credit Unions, 1992 Oct 20 (Box 178, Folder 48)
    - U.S. Senator Lloyd Bentsen, 1992 Oct 22 (Box 178, Folder 49)
    - Law enforcement Advisory Board, 1992 Nov 10 (Box 178, Folder 50)
    - Democratic Caucus (HW), 1992 Dec 9 (Box 178, Folder 51)
    - Waco Rotary Club (HW), 1993 Feb (Box 178, Folder 52)
    - Whitney Chamber of Commerce (HW), 1993 Feb (Box 178, Folder 53)
    - Black History Month (HW), 1993 Feb 21 (Box 178, Folder 54)
    - Federally Employed Women- Temple, TX (HW), 1993 May 8 (Box 178, Folder 55)
    - Waco Area Farm and Ranch Club (HW), 1993 Aug 20 (Box 178, Folder 56)
    - Exchange Sunshine Home Corporation (HW), 1994 Feb 5 (Box 178, Folder 57)
    - AIPAC Policy Conference (HW), 1994 March 14 (Box 178, Folder 58)
    - Killeen Area Chamber of Commerce (HW), 1994 Aug (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - NARFE- Temple, TX (HW), 1994 Oct 27 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Chrysler Technologies Airborne Systems (HW), 1995 June 9 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - IMPACT Aid/ Motion to Recant (HW), 1995 June 15 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - NARFE (HW), 1995 Aug 24 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Hispanic American Cultural Society (HW), 1995 Sept 23 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Hill County Community Action (HW), 1995 Oct 5 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Leadership Waco (HW), 1995 Nov 21 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - “Values Matter Most” (HW), 1995 Dec 14 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - NARFE (HW), 1996 March 16 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - John Sharp- Baylor Law Day (HW), 1996 March 30 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - Sul Ross Elementary School, 1996 May 3 (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - SABA Honors Programs (HW), 1996 May 13 (Box 179, Folder 13)
    - Retired Rubber Workers- Waco, TX (HW), 1996 Aug 10 (Box 179, Folder 14)
    - Central Texas Dental Society (HW), 1996 Aug 13 (Box 179, Folder 15)
    - Air Force Sergeant Association (HW), 1996 Aug 13 (Box 179, Folder 16)
    - Raylea E-Systems (HW), 1996 Aug 16 (Box 179, Folder 17)
    - Waco Farm and Ranch Club (HW), 1996 Aug 16 (Box 179, Folder 18)
    - Texas Farm Bureau Endorsement (HW), 1996 Aug 26 (Box 179, Folder 19)
    - Sallie Mae Loan Servicing Center (HW), 1996 Oct 1 (Box 179, Folder 20)
    - Central Texas Telephone Corporation (HW), 1996 Oct 5 (Box 179, Folder 21)
    - Korean-American Society- Killeen, TX (HW), 1996 Oct 12 (Box 179, Folder 22)
    - Secretary of the Navy (HW), 1996 Oct 14 (Box 179, Folder 23)
    - Credit Unions for 11th District (HW), 1996 Oct 15 (Box 179, Folder 24)
    - Supporting the Military Child Conference (HW), 1997 Jan 2 (Box 179, Folder 25)
    - Waco Rotary Club (HW), 1997 Jan 13 (Box 179, Folder 26)
    - Scott & White Board (HW), 1997 Jan 28 (Box 179, Folder 27)
    - A.U.S.A (HW), 1997 Jan 31 (Box 179, Folder 28)
    - Excellence in Community Policing Awards (HW), 1997 March 27 (Box 179, Folder 29)
    - Central Texas Homebuilders (HW), 1997 Nov 20 (Box 179, Folder 30)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, 1997 Dec 16 (Box 179, Folder 31)
    - Waco Hispanic Leaders (HW), 1997 Dec 16 (Box 179, Folder 32)
    - Dr. John M.R. Covey (HW), 1998 Feb 8 (Box 179, Folder 33)
    - E.B. Spike Warmer (HW), 1998 Feb 18 (Box 179, Folder 34)
    - Labor Council Meeting- Waco, TX (HW), 1998 Feb 28 (Box 179, Folder 35)
    - Abstinence Project (HW), 1998 March 16 (Box 179, Folder 36)
    - Waco Life Industries (HW), 1998 March 20 (Box 179, Folder 37)
    - Waco Rotary (HW), 1998 April 5 (Box 179, Folder 38)
    - Teen Pregnancy Presentation: Meeting the Challenge (HW), 1998 April 15 (Box 179, Folder 39)
    - Congressional Update (HW), 1998 April 16 (Box 179, Folder 40)
    - Texas Joint and Conference on Aging (HW), 1998 April 27 (Box 179, Folder 41)
    - RSVP Program, 1998 May 2 (Box 179, Folder 42)
    - Retired Sergeants, Major, and chiefs Association (HW), 1998 May 9 (Box 179, Folder 43)
    - Texas- New Mexico Company, 1998 May 21 (Box 179, Folder 44)
    - Rotary Club- Temple, TX, 1998 May 28 (Box 179, Folder 45)
    - Cherokee Home for Children- 40 years (HW), 1998 May 30 (Box 179, Folder 46)
    - Philanthropic Education Organization- Waco, TX (HW), 1998 June 3 (Box 179, Folder 47)
    - Texas Agricultural Experiment Station (HW), 1998 Aug 13 (Box 179, Folder 48)
    - Major General Morris Boyd Introduction (HW), 1998 Aug 13 (Box 179, Folder 49)
    - Harker Heights Chamber of Commerce (HW), 1998 Aug 27 (Box 179, Folder 50)
    - Temple Business League (HW), 1998 Nov 9 (Box 179, Folder 51)
    - Ferguson Enterprise, INC. (HW), 1998 Nov 23 (Box 179, Folder 52)
    - Waco [C of C Directors] (HW), 1999 Jan 12 (Box 179, Folder 53)
    - Baylor Leadership Council (HW), 1999 Feb 16 (Box 179, Folder 54)
    - Advisory Group (HW), 1999 Feb 16 (Box 179, Folder 55)
    - African-American Ministers (HW), 1999 Feb 16 (Box 179, Folder 56)
    - Veterans Leaders (HW), 1999 Feb 16 (Box 179, Folder 57)
    - Defense System Management (HW), 1999 Feb 17 (Box 179, Folder 58)
    - AUSA (W), 1999 Feb 17 (Box 179, Folder 59)
    - Waco Rotary Club (HW), 1999 April 4 (Box 179, Folder 60)
    - Killeen Government Affairs Committee(HW), 1999 April 6 (Box 179, Folder 61)
    - Belton/ Temple Heart Association (HW), 1999 May 7 (Box 179, Folder 62)
    - Sallie May/ James Branch Scholarship (HW), 1999 May 10 (Box 179, Folder 63)
    - National Association of Homebuilders, 1999 May 13 (Box 179, Folder 64)
    - National Center for Missing and Exploited Children (HW), 1999 May 25 (Box 179, Folder 65)
    - Heart of Texas (HW), 1999 June 5 (Box 179, Folder 66)
    - Temple Chamber of Commerce Government Affairs, 1999 Aug 17 (Box 179, Folder 67)
    - Trane Company Speech, 1999 Sept 28 (Box 179, Folder 68)
    - American Legion- District 6 (HW), 1999 Oct 9 (Box 179, Folder 69)
    - Economic Development Administration (HW), 1999 Oct 11 (Box 179, Folder 70)
    - Report on 1999 Session/ What Lies Ahead in 2000 (HW), 1999 Dec (Box 179, Folder 71)
    - Social Security and Medicare (HW), 1999 (Box 179, Folder 72)
    - Gun-Safety Laws (HW), 1999 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Social Security (HW), 1999 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Independent Cattleman’s Association (HW), 2000 Jan 11 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Killeen Rotary Club (HW), 2000 Jan 12 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Senior Texans on Patrol (HW), 2000 Jan 19 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - E & T Enterprises (HW), 2000 March 31 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Texas AFL-CIO Committee (HW), 2000 April 18 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Brazos Electric Company (HW), 2000 April 26 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Waco Rotary (HW), 2000 May 1 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Leadership Waco (HW), 2000 Nov 21 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Team Leadership Waco (HW), 2000 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Senior Installation Leader Conference (HW), 2000 Jan 11 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Presidential Community Initiative (HW), 2001 April 26 (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Presidential Classroom for Young Americans, 2001 June 12 (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Temple-Cardio Res. Institute (HW), 2001 Aug 28 (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - Capitol Area Homebuilders- Georgetown, TX, 2002 Feb 19 (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - Town Hall Meetings (HW), 2002 March 11 (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - Bosque County Town Hall Meeting (HW), 2002 March 11 (Box 180, Folder 18)
    - Chamber of Commerce (HW), 2002 March 21 (Box 180, Folder 19)
    - McLennan Community College Faculty (HW), 2002 May 3 (Box 180, Folder 20)
    - McLennan Community College Students (HW), 2002 May 3 (Box 180, Folder 21)
    - Farm Bureau (HW), 2002 June 6 (Box 180, Folder 22)
    - HOTCOG- Waco, TX (HW), 2002 Aug 22 (Box 180, Folder 23)
    - AARP (HW), 2002 Oct 9 (Box 180, Folder 24)
    - New Democratic Members (HW), 2002 Nov 12 (Box 180, Folder 25)
    - Project OLR- Temple, TX (HW), 2002 (Box 180, Folder 26)
    - Waco City Council (HW), 2002 (Box 180, Folder 27)
    - Waco Lions Club (HW), 2002 (Box 180, Folder 28)
    - Hindu Temple of Central Texas (HW), 2003 Feb 15 (Box 180, Folder 29)
    - Temple Rotary (HW), 2003 Aug 25 (Box 180, Folder 30)
    - [Northcrup] Rotary Club (HW), 2004 Jan 1 (Box 180, Folder 31)
    - Cen-Tex Hispanic Chamber Cinco de Mayo, 2004 May 1 (Box 180, Folder 32)
    - Brazos Valley Council of Governments (HW), 2004 July 1 (Box 180, Folder 33)
    - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada, 2005 April 19 (Box 180, Folder 34)
    - LULAC Council (HW), 2006 Feb 11 (Box 180, Folder 35)
    - Junior Leadership Brazos — College Station, TX, 2006 March 20 (Box 180, Folder 36)
    - Bryan- Humana Meeting (HW), 2005 April 15 (Box 180, Folder 37)
    - Houston Vets Town Hall Meeting, 2008 Feb 18 (Box 180, Folder 38)
    - Veterans Meeting, 2009 (Box 180, Folder 39)
    - AHA; Temple Chapter (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 40)
    - Army Directors of Public Works (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 41)
    - B/CS Chamber of Commerce (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 42)
    - BCS Association of Realtors (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 43)
    - Cameron Town Hall Meeting (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 44)
    - Central Texas Telephone Co-op (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 45)
    - Dr. Robert Gates Speech (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 46)
    - Federal Aviation Administration/ Airfield Project (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 47)
    - Greater Houston Partnership (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 48)
    - Heart of Texas Business Resource Center/ Small Business Week (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 49)
    - Hood County Town Hall (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 50)
    - “How I Survived the 80’s” (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 51)
    - IBM (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 52)
    - “Insuring Safe Schools: Stopping Violence Before it Starts as a Parent” (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 53)
    - International Association of Personnel in Employment Security (IAPES) (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 54)
    - Introduction of Lt. General Tom Metz, undated (Box 180, Folder 55)
    - Johnson County Town Halls (Conversations) (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 56)
    - Killeen Chamber of Commerce (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 57)
    - Killeen Chamber of Commerce (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 58)
    - Killeen Lion’s Club (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 59)
    - Korean 50th Anniversary of Armistice, undated (Box 180, Folder 60)
    - Lampasas Farm Bureau (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 61)
    - Leadership- Temple, TX (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 62)
    - Memorial Day Eve Speech (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 63)
    - NAACP Speech, undated (Box 180, Folder 64)
    - National Youth Leadership Tour on Security & Defense (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 65)
    - “Partnering with Private Enterprise: The Congressional Perspective” (HW), undated (Box 180, Folder 66)
    - Policy Speech (HW), undated (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Rapoport Academy (HW), undated (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Rotary Club Speech (HW), undated (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Rural Health Care, undated (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - School Superintendent (HW), undated (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Speech to Women’s Business Group, undated (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Students (HW), undated (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Temple Chamber of Commerce (HW), undated (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Town Halls (HW), undated (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - U.S Army War College (HW), undated (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - VA Health Care, undated (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-2010, undated; 10
    - Gatesville, TX (HW), 1991 Jan 26 (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Economic Opportunities Advancement Corporation (HW), 1991 April 15 (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Coryell County Museum (HW), 1991 April 20 (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Lessons of the Persian Gulf War, 1991 May 6 (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - POW/ MIA Day (HW), 1991 Sept 20 (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - Congressional Record, 1991 Oct 24 (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - Desert Storm (HW), 1991 (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - Desert Storm/ Texas St. Guard (HW), 1991 (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - Bartlett, TX (HW), 1992 Feb 8 (Box 181, Folder 20)
    - Roast of Judge John Hill (HW), 1992 June 20 (Box 181, Folder 21)
    - Tennessee and Texas, 1992 Aug 27 (Box 181, Folder 22)
    - Observations of Congress (HW), 1992 Oct (Box 181, Folder 23)
    - Jay Belew (HW), 1992 Oct 17 (Box 181, Folder 24)
    - AJ Moore High School Reunion- Waco, TX (HW), 1993 July 2 (Box 181, Folder 25)
    - Health Care Plan- President Clinton (HW), 1993 Sept 22 (Box 181, Folder 26)
    - “The National Debt — Is it Just a Nagging Problem or a Real Threat to our Country’s Future?” (HW), 1993 (Box 181, Folder 27)
    - Ann Richards (HW), 1994 Oct 24 (Box 181, Folder 28)
    - Ann Richards (HW), 1994 Nov (Box 181, Folder 29)
    - Seniors In the 1960s and 1990s, 1995 Aug 19 (Box 181, Folder 30)
    - “A Dime’s Worth of Difference?” (HW), 1995 Aug 21 (Box 181, Folder 31)
    - Congressional Observations (HW), 1995 Aug (Box 181, Folder 32)
    - Medicare, 1995 Oct 26 (Box 181, Folder 33)
    - Bosnian Peace Treaty (HW), 1995 Nov 21 (Box 181, Folder 34)
    - Issue Update (HW), 1995 (Box 181, Folder 35)
    - News Conference (HW), 1996 Feb 2 (Box 181, Folder 36)
    - John Spratt- Ranking member of the Budget Committee (HW), 1996 April 18 (Box 181, Folder 37)
    - Report on 104th Congress (HW), 1996 Oct 10 (Box 181, Folder 38)
    - Congressional Reflections (HW), 1996 (Box 181, Folder 39)
    - Fort Worth (HW), 1996 (Box 181, Folder 40)
    - Whitney, TX (HW), 1997 Jan 17 (Box 181, Folder 41)
    - Honorable Louis Caldera (HW), 1998 Sept 29 (Box 181, Folder 42)
    - Hyde Resolution, 1998 Oct 8 (Box 181, Folder 43)
    - Attacks on Church- State Separation- Boston, MA (HW), 1998 Nov 13 (Box 181, Folder 44)
    - Nomination of Cal Dooley, 1998 Nov 16 (Box 181, Folder 45)
    - House Highway Bill (HW), 1998 (Box 181, Folder 46)
    - David Dickson (HW), 1999 Jan 11 (Box 181, Folder 47)
    - Presidential Classroom (HW), 1999 Jan 26 (Box 181, Folder 48)
    - Bipartisan Appropriations Bill (HW), 1999 Feb 2 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - “Concerns About Our Political Process from a Representative Perspective” (HW), 1999 Feb 5 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Observations on Defense (HW), 1999 Feb 5 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - National Defense University (HW), 1999 Sept 29 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - NAFIS (HW), 1999 Oct 18 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - L.U.L.A.C (HW), 1999 Oct 23 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Kosovo (HW), 1999 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Republican Roast (HW), 1999 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Prescription Drug Report- Part III (HW), 2000 Jan 13 (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Brent Walker, EX Director of the Joint Baptist Committee on Public Affairs, 2000 March 5 (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Pecan Valley Estates (HW), 2000 March 17 (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - Texas Housing, 2000 April 19 (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - Drayton & Elizabeth McLane (HW), 2000 Aug 24 (Box 182, Folder 13)
    - Second the Nomination of Dave Bonior as the Democratic Whip, 2000 Nov 14 (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - Bill Daley- Ballot Discussion (HW), 2000 Nov 25 (Box 182, Folder 15)
    - “The Role of Congress in Defense” (HW), 2001 Nov 6 (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - “My Observations Since September 11” (HW), 2001 (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - “Charitable Choice, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 18)
    - Retirement of Doug [Kleypas] (HW), 2002 Jan 5 (Box 182, Folder 19)
    - Democratic Retreat, 2002 Jan 26 (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - Introduction of the Honorable Thomas E. White, 2002 Feb 14 (Box 182, Folder 21)
    - Free Flight Systems, 2002 March 11 (Box 182, Folder 22)
    - Permanent Repeal of the Estate Tax, 2002 June 6 (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - Ron Kirk Intro, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 24)
    - Highway Funding, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 25)
    - America’s Response to Terrorism, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 26)
    - Congressional Update, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 27)
    - Texas Community Developments(HW), 2003 (Box 182, Folder 28)
    - Ban on Partial-Birth Abortion, 2003 (Box 182, Folder 29)
    - Ham Creek Project- Johnson County, TX, 2004 Feb 29 (Box 182, Folder 30)
    - Killeen, TX (HW), 2004 July 1 (Box 182, Folder 31)
    - Perchlorate Speech, 2004 (Box 182, Folder 32)
    - Cleburne Rotary Club, c. 2005 (Box 182, Folder 33)
    - Energy Policy Act of 2005: One Year Later, A Look to the Future- Funding for Energy Programs (Box 182, Folder 34)
    - Legislative Update- 3 Parts (HW), 2006 Jan 5 (Box 182, Folder 35)
    - Cuts in College Student Financial Aid, 2006 Feb 23 (Box 182, Folder 36)
    - Remembrance of September 11th, 2006 Sept 9 (Box 182, Folder 37)
    - Hood County- Appropriations Bill (HW), 2007 (Box 182, Folder 38)
    - Possible VP Statement, c.2007 (Box 182, Folder 39)
    - Residential Community Initiative (RCI), Army Housing Program, 2008 May 9 (Box 182, Folder 40)
    - Texas Farm Bureau (HW), 2008 (Box 182, Folder 41)
    - Lake Whitney Chamber of Commerce, 2009 (Box 182, Folder 42)
    - Eliz/Fundraise/Pre-Primaries (HW), 2010 Jan 15 (Box 182, Folder 43)
    - 9/11 Anniversary, undated (Box 182, Folder 44)
    - 9/11 (September 11th) Firemen & Policemen, undated (Box 182, Folder 45)